cinepunch.in 2015-06-28

# Privacy Policy | Cine Punch

Welcome to **cinepunch.in**. We always value your confidentiality and wish to let you know what information we gather and what we make with it.

We make changes to our Privacy policy on a regular basis. We venture to post the changes in our policy sooner than they become more effective. This privacy policy condition gets applied to all the information we collect and receive from you and as well as from other source.

**Data Collected by Cinepunch.in**

**Cinepunch.in** includes many spots where user can submit their information to us. Also, our comprised features collect information from our registered users and other visitors automatically.

**Data Offered to  Cine Punch**

**Cine Punch  **features certain areas where we request user to provide information to our website.

**Registration Process**

To use more specialized features of **cine punch** , the user need to register with us.  For registration, we render various options and also simple sign for Email Subscription that requires no products or service. While registering, the users have to supply his/her “Contact information” (name, Email ID, Phone numbers) and some demographic information (Country, State, Place). The user may be asked to enter and email address and password for future reference.  If interested, users can render us their interest, preferences on acting and music optionally.

**Communication between users and Cine Punch**

To keep our user updated with our services, we fling Emails and other announcements that are necessary for proper functioning and subscription service. For supplementary information, we offer the members an option to join out Emailing list. Moreover, we provide an alternative option to receive alerts from third part sponsors. Every mail from cinpepunch.in comes with an instruction set to unsubscribe from our mailing list.

We also have special features where users can submit their own information to us in terms of queries and other related problems. We will hang on to users request and other information for **cinepunch.in** internal purpose and to serve you better.

**Interactive Features:**

**Cinepunch.in** includes Chat rooms and message board as interactive characteristics. Keep in mind that all personal information that is shared via interactive features will get displayed publicly and our website is not responsible for your information including your Name and Email address.  We may pile up that information for our analysis purpose of website traffic. But it is purely to verify obscenity, offense and right to remove at any time. We will not file such information in individual basics.

**Surveys:**

Occasionally, **cinepunch.in** requests their users to take part in voluntary surveys. The intention of those surveys is to offers better user experience and offered information gets associated with member name for future use. Personal information collected will be used only by cinepunch.in and will not be revealed at any cost.

**Automatic data Collection:**

**Cookies:**

**Cinepunch.in** makes use of technology of software called “Cookies” for numerous purposes. We commonly use “Session” cookies that valid up to the complete duration of the users in online and that identifies whether the users is registered to our website. This is to ensure the identity of the user and to deliver the music, restricts misusing of the user’s accounts. A session cookie also facilitates us to promote surveys and other direct communication with users. A “Persistent” cookie stays with you even after session expiry. They assist in Sign-In by remembering the username and password for future log-in attempts. It will be activated only when the user selects this option at the time of Sign-in. Any other can deselect this cookie at any time.

**Others:**

To personalize our service more effectively, we capture some data as searches of users and results. Additionally, we gather IP address, Connection speed, Date and time for internal purpose of **cinepunch.in** such as trend analysis, internal audit and other system administration functions.

**Third Party Advertising and Cookies:**

During advertisement serving to c **inepunch**. **in** , our third party advertisers may possibly places a unique “Cookies” on your browser.

**With whom we share your Data:**

We never share your personal information with other companies apart from out Tie-up agencies those help us in offering quality service to you, all of which agrees to use it confidentially and make it secured. Also, entities into which our **cinepunch.in** is merged can use your personal information under the terms of our privacy policy. We also disclose our maintained information when required to do so by law, for example, in response to court order and other legal obligation, in response to request of enforcement agency. In some cases, we believe that our disclosed information is necessary to identify and contact to bring legal action again someone who cause grievance to property and rights of **cinepunch.in**. We may make use of collective demographic information of our audience to improve our service in terms of marketing.

**Links:**

We are not responsible for other website links that may get displayed in our **cinepunch.in**. Also, we are not responsible for those websites, their privacy policies and the way they treat user’s information. Please check out their terms and policies before sharing your personal information over their websites.

**Downloads:**

We often link to other websites that may support downloads. Cine Punch will not be responsible for the downloadable materials in their websites. Also, we are not responsible for the privacy policy and legalities attaching these downloads in the websites that our users may refer in our discussion and forums. These downloads as referred in privacy policy can be images, videos, games, software and any other application files.

  * Google, as a third party vendor is using cookies to serve ads on the website.
  * Google’s use of DART cookies enable it to serve ads to the users based on their frequent visit of the websites and other websites over the internet.
  * User may opt out from the use of these DART cookies by visiting Google ad and Content Network Privacy policy.

We apply third-party advertising with other companies to serve ads when users visit our website **cinepunch.in**. These companies may also use information about your visit to the website in order to offer enhanced advertising of Services and Products that may grab your attention.
